뭐 보는 거야?
What are you looking at?
내 1차 대전 영화 포스터
와서 봐
A poster for that WWI movie I'm in.
Check it out.
와! 진짜 폭력적이다!
Wow! It looks really violent!
알아, 극장에서 곧 상영해
I know. I'm coming soon
to a theater near you.
내가 THX 영화에 나와!
어린이용 배우가 아니라고!
I'm in THX.
I'm unsuitable for children!
- 빨리 보고 싶다
- 오스카상 받을지도 모른대
-I cannot wait to see this.
-It's generating Oscar buzz.
- 그 소문 내가 낸 거야!
- 내가 낸 줄 알았는데!
-I started that!
-I thought I did!
매니저가 그러는데
I just talked to my agent..
다음 주에 시사회래
너희들 모두 초대할게!
and the premiere is next week
and you're all invited!
- 리무진 타고 가는 거야?
- 당연하지!
-Will we take a limo?
-Sure!
드디어 장례식 아닐 때
한 번 타보는군
I love taking limos
when nobody died.
난 못 갈 거 같아
Well, I won't be able to come.
참고로 말하는데
오늘이 예정일이거든
For those who haven't checked
their calendars, today's my due date.
너도 같이 가야지
리무진에서 애 낳을지도 모르잖아
You should come.
Maybe you'll have the baby in the limo.
그러면 애가 처음 몇 달간은
우리가 부자인 줄 알 거야
That way for the first few moments of her
life, she'll think we're really fancy.
그동안 너무 잘 해줘서
다들 고마워
I want to thank you guys
for how great you've been during this.
너희 없었으면 못해냈을 거야
지난 열 달 동안 너무 행복했어
I couldn't have done it without you.
I loved these last 9 months.
낳아서 기르는 일도
기다려지지만
I'm looking forward
to the next part..
지난 열 달이 정말 그리울 거야
I am really gonna miss
being pregnant.
알아, 아직도 안 나왔어
That's right. Still no baby.
왜 그래?
배불뚝이 임산부가
What's the matter? Is the puffy,
sweaty pregnant lady..
너희들 휴식시간을 방해한 거야?
disturbing your precious
coffee time?
야, 나도 앉게 좀 비켜 봐
Come on, people, make some room.
이 자리가 더 편하지 않겠어?
Sweetie, maybe you'd be
more comfortable here.
너!
You.
나를 이 모양으로
만들어 놓고도 모자라?
Like you haven't done enough.
힘든 거 알아
할 수만 있다면 뭐든 하고 싶어
I know you're miserable.
I wish there was something I could do.
내가 해마였으면 좋겠어
I wish I were a sea horse.
해마는 수컷이 새끼를 낳거든
Because with sea horses, it's the male.
They carry the babies.
게다가 바다 속 멀리
떨어져 있을 테니까
And then also,
I'd be far away in the sea.
미치겠다
God.
내 인생에 이렇게 불편하기는
첨이야
I have never been so uncomfortable
in my entire life.
이해해, 나도 마지막 달에는...
I know. I remember toward the end..
이야기 진짜 재밌다
아이스티 좀 갖다주고 말할래?
That's a great story. Tell it while
you're getting me some iced tea.
야, 여기서 나가!
나가, 나가, 나가!
Oh, God, get out!
Get out, get out, get out!
가자
Let's.
프렌즈 시즌 8
'레이첼의 지연출산'
아직도 안 낳았어?
Hey, did you have the baby yet?
깔고 앉아줄까?
정말 그렇게 해 줄까?
Do you want me to sit on you?
Because I'll do it.
- 이 시간에 웬 일이야?
- 회사에서, 집에 가래
-What are you doing here?
-They sent me home from work.
"출산 휴가 오늘부터 받아요
쉬어야죠" 그러더라
They said, "Start your maternity
leave now. Just rest."
다 핑계 대는 헛소리야!
You know what? Screw them!
회사에서 안 받아주면
여기서 너희랑 놀지 뭐
If they don't want me there,
I'll hang out with you guys.
아니면 자원봉사 해
Or you could do volunteer work.
- 여보세요?
- 조이, 에스텔이야
-Hello?
-Joey, it's Estelle.
시사회 입장권 2장 얻었어
I was able to get you and one guest
tickets to your premiere.
- 6장 받을 수 있다고 했잖아요
- 4장은 내가 팔아먹었지
-You told me I could have six tickets.
-I sold four on eBay.
핫가이 372 옆자리야
You'll be sitting next to HotGuy 372.
그래서 손님 1명만
초대하라구요?
So that's it? I only get
to bring one guest?
그래, 나 몇 시에
데리러 올 거야?
Yeah. What time you
wanna pick me up?
여보세요?
Hello?
들었어?
1명밖에 못 데려간대
You hear that?
I only get one extra ticket to my premiere.
그러니까 너희 셋 하고
로스 중에서 1명 골라야 해
So somehow I have to pick
between you three and Ross.
- 나는 왜 빼?
- 못 간다면서
-What about me?
-You said you didn't want to go.
못 가지만 무시당하고 싶진 않아
I don't. But I would
still like to be acknowledged.
- 임신했지 투명인간은 아니잖아?
- 걱정마, 확실히 눈에 보이니까
-Because I'm pregnant, I'm invisible?
-Definitely not invisible.
로스는 이 자리에 없으니까 빼
Ross didn't care enough
to be here, so he's out.
- 게으르면 못 챙겨 먹는거야
- 로스 지금 수업 중이야
-You snooze, you lose.
-He's not snoozing. He's teaching.
그게 그거지
Well, then somebody's snoozing.
굳이 강조하려는 건 아니지만
나를 선택하면
And, Joey, not that this should affect
you at all, but if you pick me..
배꼽 위로 오는 금장식
드레스 입을 거야
I was planning on wearing
a sequin dress cut down to here.
- 난 그런 옷 본 적 없는데
- 유명스타랑 너랑 같냐?
-I haven't seen this dress.
-Star in a movie.
네 마음에 귀를 기울이고
정말 원하는 사람이 누군지 봐
Pick whoever you want. Listen
to your heart. What does it tell you?
피비, 피비, 피비
Phoebe. Phoebe. Phoebe.
글쎄
Well..
챈들러를 데려가고 싶어
I think I want to take Chandler.
피비, 피비, 피비...
Phoebe, Phoebe, Phoebe.
- 나를 데려간다구?
- 응, 모두 다 데려가고 싶지만
-You want to take me?
-Yeah, I wish I could take everybody.
챈들러가 정말 도움을
많이 줬으니까
But Chandler's always
supported my career.
연기수업료랑 사진값도
대신 내주고
He's paid for acting classes,
headshots and stuff.
이렇게라도 갚으려고
This will be my way
of paying you back.
그래서 그 돈 안갚는다구?
So you're never actually
going to pay me back?
사진값 좀 내줬다고
챈들러를 데려간단 말이야?
Just because he paid for your headshots,
you're gonna take him?
내가 무슨 옷 입을지
아직 이해를 못한 모양인데
I don't think you're comprehending
just how slutty this dress is.
돈 문제만이 아냐
난 전부 다 말하는 거야
It's not just the stuff he paid for.
It's everything, you know?
대사 연습도 같이 해주고
오디션에도 같이 가줬어
He read lines with me. He went with me
on auditions when I was nervous.
오디션에 떨어지면
위로도 해주고
Then he consoled me
after I didn't get parts that I wanted.
나 자신도 나를 믿지 않을 때
챈들러는 믿어줬어
You always believed in me, man,
even when I didn't.
난 니가 해낼 줄 알았어
정말 자랑스러워
I always knew you were gonna make it.
I'm so proud of you.
고마워, 정말
Thanks, that means a lot to me.
얘네들이 네 드레스 입어야
하는 거 아냐?
Mon, maybe one of these guys
wants to wear your dress.
- 가서 면도해야지
- 난 가서, 침 뱉어야지
-I'm gonna go shave.
-Yeah, well, I'm gonna go spit.
난 가서 오줌 눠야지
I have to pee.
내가 안 나오면 화장실 향수 냄새에
질식해 죽은 줄 알아
If I don't come out, it's because I've
choked to death on the potpourri stink.
레이첼 코 막고 입으로 훅 불면
아기가 나오지 않을까?
You hold her nose, I'll blow in her
mouth and the kid'll just.. out of her.
1주일이나 늦네
오늘 낳아야 하는데
She's a week late.
She's got to have it today.
글쎄, 시간이 좀
걸릴 거 같은데
I don't know. I think
it's still gonna be a while.
우리 내기할래?
Care to make it interesting?
- 난 '내일 낳는다'에 건다
- 좋았어
-I bet you she'll have it tomorrow.
-You're on.
- 얼마 걸 거야?
- 십만 달러
-Okay, how much?
-One hundred thousand dollars.
- 50달러 어때?
- 비밀 금고에서 돈 좀 빼야겠다
-How about 50 bucks?
-I'll call Zurich and move some money.
누가 나 일으켜줄 차례야?
All right, whose turn is it
to help me get up?
아무도 없다
No one's here.
죽겠네!
Oh, damn it!
영화 시사회
"저 건너편에"
정말 끝내준다!
사진도 찍혔어, 나 어떠냐?
This is exciting. So glamorous! People
taking our picture. How do I look?
- 좀 크다
- 뭐?
-A little tall.
-What?
내가 커 보이게
몸 좀 쭈그릴래?
Would you crouch down a bit
so that I look taller?
그렇지
There you go.
정말 대단하다
It's just so glamorous.
모니카? 레이첼 여깄어
Oh, hey, Mon? Rach is here.
아직도 임신 중이네
And you're still pregnant.
미안, 얼마나 힘든지 알아
I'm sorry. I know
how uncomfortable you are.
너 정말 멋져
꼭 50달러처럼
You know what? You look great.
Yeah, like 50 bucks.
또 오줌 마려, 애가 내 방광을
장난감처럼 막 주무르나 봐
I have to go pee. Apparently this baby
thinks my bladder is a squeeze toy.
열받아, 50달러 여깄어
Damn it. Here's your 50 bucks.
니가 지니까 재밌다
참, 너 지는 거 좋아하던가?
That's interesting that you lost.
Now, I forget, do you like to lose?
알았어, 그만 해
All right, stop it.
- 내일 낳는다에 두 배 건다
- 좋아
-Double or nothing she has it tomorrow.
-Fine.
그때까지 세종대왕님은
여기서 쉬시겠어요?
Until then, General Grant, why don't
you set up camp.. right there?
- 레이첼 어딨어? 병원 가야지
- 화장실
-Rachel here? We have an appointment.
-In the bathroom.
- 약속 늦겠다
- 금방 나가!
-Rach, we gotta go.
-In a minute!
사람들이 우리 사이를 물으면
뭐라고 대답할지 모르겠어
People ask why we're not together.
I just don't know what to tell them.
가자
All right, let's go.
잠깐만
Oh, wait a minute.
오줌을 한 번 더 눠야 할까?
Do I have to pee again?
아냐, 괜찮아
No, I'm good.
옷 먼저 갈아입을래?
Do you want to go change first?
의사 선생님이 기다려
주실 거야, 서둘러
The doctor's staying open late for us,
but if you hurry..
- 아냐, 괜찮아
- 옷이 좀 이상하지 않아?
-No, I'm fine.
-You don't think that's inappropriate?
- 뭐가?
- 제발 열 받게 하지 마
-What?
-Good God, man. Don't anger it.
로스, 밖에 지금 38도야
몇 주만에 처음으로 내가...
Ross, it is 100 degrees outside.
For the first time in weeks, I am..
알았어, 원하는 대로 해
니가 엄마니까
Fine. Whatever you want.
You're the mommy.
제발! "엄마"라고 부르지마
No! Don't call me "Mommy."
네 엄마한테 그러는 것도
충분히 지겨워
It's bad enough you call
your own mother that.
실은 레이첼 말에 공감해
I'm actually with her on this one.
얼른, 로스
늦겠다
Come on, Ross.
We're gonna be late.
누구 로스 되고 싶은
사람 있어?
Either of you want to be Ross?
적이 누구인지 안다고 생각했는데
그게 너일 줄이야
I thought I knew who the enemy was,
but it was you.
잘 봐
이제 내 전투장면 나와
Okay, this is it. This is
my big fight scene coming up.
나는 82사단을 위해 싸운다
I'm fighting for every man
in the 82nd Ground Division.
로스?
하나 물어봐도 돼?
Ross?
Can I ask you something?
캐롤이 벤 임신했을 때
When Carol was pregnant with Ben..
그때도 이렇게 짜증나게 굴었어?
were you this irritating?
- 뭐라구?
- 아냐, 그냥 니가 좀
-Excuse me?
-Nothing. You're just..
너 요즘 나한테 좀 야박해
널 짜증나게 하는 거 아냐
You've been a little short with me
lately. I'm not trying to irritate you.
그럼 남 짜증나게 하는 거
타고났나 보네
Well, then, you must have
a natural talent for it.
의사 선생님 곧 오시니까
그때까지 입다물고 있자
The doctor will be in soon.
Why don't we not speak until then?
좋아
Okay.
제발, 숨 좀 크게 쉬어, 로스
그래 그렇게
Seriously. Breathe louder, Ross.
That's great.
어떻게 하면 반은 인간이고
반은 악마인 사람을 낳는지
We should ask the doctor
if she even knows..
의사 선생님한테 물어봐야겠다
how to deliver a baby
that's half human, half pure evil!
- 롱 선생님, 안녕하세요?
- 의사한테는 친절하네
-Hi, Dr. Long. How are you?
-You're nice to her.
약 갖고 있잖아
She has the drugs.
빨리 한 번 볼까요?
We'll do a quick check.
8일이나 늦었죠?
많이 힘드시겠어요
Eight days late, huh?
You must be getting uncomfortable.
네, 약간요
Yeah, just a tad.
80% 정도 왔다고 보시면 돼요
시간이 좀 더 걸릴 거예요
You're 80% effaced. You're on your way.
It still could last a while.
- 출산을 당기는 방법도 있는데
- 가르쳐 주세요!
-There are ways to help things along.
-Do them!
집에서도 할 수 있는
방법들인데요
Actually, they're things
that you can do. Home remedies.
제 경험으로는 상당히
효과적이더라구요
In my experience, I've found
some are very effective.
- 뭐든지 할 준비가 돼 있어요
- 허브 티를 많이 드시고
-Well, we are ready to try anything.
-There's an herbal tea you can drink.
피마자 기름을 드셔도 좋고
매운 음식도 효과가 있어요
You can take some castor oil.
There's spicy foods.
전부 다 할게요
We will do all of those.
- 그리고 오래 걸으세요
- 염려 마세요
-Taking a long walk.
-Good. Done.
그래도 가장 효과적인 것은
섹스하는 거예요
And there's the one that's
proved most effective: sex.
꿈도 꾸지 마!
You've got to be kidding me!
잘 했어, 조이!
훌륭해! 최고야!
Good job, Joe! Well done! Top-notch!
- 좋았어? 정말로?
- 그럼!
-You liked it? You really liked it?
-Oh, yeah!
- 정확히 어느 부분이 좋았어?
- 전부 다! 얼른 가자
-Well, which part exactly?
-The whole thing! Here we go!
아냐, 특별한 부분을 말해 봐
No, no, no. Give me some specifics.
난 그 특별한 부분들이 좋더라
특별한 부분들이 최고였어
I loved the specifics.
The specifics were the best part.
캥거루 나오는 장면 어떻든?
괜찮았어?
Hey, what about the scene with
the kangaroo? Did you like that part?
1차 대전 영화에
캥거루가 나와서 깜짝 놀랬어
I was surprised to see a kangaroo
in a World War I epic.
너 잤잖아!
You fell asleep!
캥거루는 무슨 캥거루야!
내가 제안했는데 묵살됐다구!
There was no kangaroo! They didn't
take any of my suggestions!
- 세상에, 자다니 믿을 수가 없어
- 나도 못 믿겠어
-I can't believe you fell asleep.
-I can't believe it either.
혹시 안 잔 거 아닐까?
Maybe it didn't happen.
아니면 네가 잠들어서
그걸 꿈에서 본 거 아냐?
Maybe you fell asleep
and dreamt the whole thing.
그래서 지금 이 이야기도
그 꿈의 일부인 거지
And this conversation we're having
right now is part of that dream.
일어나, 조이!
Wake up, Joe!
- 와줘서 고맙다, 잘 가
- 그러지 마, 잘못했어
-Thanks for coming. See you later.
-Don't go. I'm so sorry.
봐, 이 남자도 잤어!
이 사람한테 화내!
Look, this guy fell asleep!
He fell asleep too! Be mad at him!
아니면 구급차 불러!
Or call an ambulance!
의사가 뭐래?
아기가 언제 나올 거래?
What did the doctor say?
Any news on when the baby will come?
출산을 촉진하는 방법만
알려줬어
No. She gave us ideas
on how to induce labor.
전부 다 해봤는데
We tried them all.
걷기도 하고, 차도 마시고
매운 것도 먹었는데, 그대로야
We went for a walk, we tried tea,
castor oil, spicy food. Nothing worked.
안 해본 게 딱 하나 있지
There is one thing we didn't try.
근데 누가 그걸
아주 끔찍하게 생각해서
But someone thinks that
that will open up a can of worms.
그거 해
그럼 오늘 애 낳을거야
If it's gonna help
bring the baby here, today..
난 빨리 하는 게 좋다고
생각해
I think you should do it.
- 섹스 하는 거야
- 얼른 해!
-It's sex.
-Do it!
- 모니카
- 너무 오래 기다렸잖아
-Monica.
-It's been a really long time for you.
여자도 욕구가 있는 거야
해, 너의 욕구를 찾아
I mean, women have needs.
Do it. Get yours.
글쎄올시다
Oh, I don't know about that.
둘이 섹스 하고 나면
그 뒷감당을 어떻게 하려구?
I think if the two of you had sex, the
repercussions would be catastrophic.
좋아, 현실적으로 생각하자
All right, let's be practical.
로스가 안 하겠다면
세상에 남자가 한 명은 아니니까
If Ross isn't willing, he's not
the only guy you can have sex with.
챈들러 빌려줄게
챈들러도 잘 해
You could borrow Chandler.
Chandler is good.
됐어, 그건 싫어
Okay, okay. Yeah,
I don't think I wanna do that.
정말이야? 내 말은
You sure? I'm just saying..
아기 머리가 더 작아지지
않는다는 거지
the baby's head
isn't getting any smaller.
모니카, 너 대체 왜 그래?
Monica, what is the matter with you?
- 그냥 애를 오늘 낳았으면 해서
- 왜 오늘이야?
-I just want the baby to be born today.
-Why today?
좋아, 말할게
Okay, fine.
네가 '오늘 애 낳는다'에 피비랑
내기했어, 지기 싫단 말이야
I bet Phoebe that you're gonna have
the baby, and I don't want to lose.
뭐? 친구가 이렇게 힘들어하는데
그걸로 돈을 번단 말이야?
What? While she's been going through
this hell, you've been making money?
이렇게 비참한 친구를 두고
내기를 했어?
You're betting on your friend
staying in this misery?
- 나도 내기할래
- 뭐?
-I'll take that bet.
-What?
힘들어 죽겠는데
돈이라도 벌어야지
I'm miserable. I may as well
make some money out of it.
그럼 나도 끼어도 돼?
Can I get some of that action?
나 혼자 너희들을 상대하라구?
I'm betting against all of you?
정말 내일은 낳을 거 같애
I really feel like
tomorrow it's gonna happen.
좋아
Okay.
60, 80, 100
Sixty, 80, 100.
그리고 50
And 50.
그리고 둘
And two.
오케이
Yeah, baby.
헤이, 잠자는 숲 속의 미녀
Hey, Sleeping Beauty.
어디 갔었어?
얘기 좀 하자, 내가 잘못했어
Where have you been?
I want to talk to you. I still feel bad.
싫어, 기분이 안좋아?
왜, 잠이 부족하냐?
Oh, no. Were you upset?
Did you lose sleep?
진짜 잘못했다
I'm so sorry.
빚 청산하러 왔어
니가 나한테 해준 게 많으니까
The reason I came over is to settle things
between us. You've done a lot for me.
시사회로 다 갚으려고 했는데
니가 그걸 놓쳤으니
I wanted to pay you back
with the premiere, but you missed it.
- 얼마 갚으면 되지?
- 뭘?
-So how much do I owe you?
-What?
- 너한테 빚지기 싫어
- 나한테 빚진 거 없어
-I don't want to owe you anything.
-You don't owe me.
- 네 돈 받는 거...
- 계산하자구!
-I don't want your..
-We're doing this!
내 첫 사진값 내줬고
얼마였지?
You got me my first headshots.
How much?
- 몰라, $500
- $500, 또 뭐 있지?
-I don't know, $500.
-Okay, $500. What else?
두 번째 사진값도 냈지
그 엄청 큰 눈곱 낀 사진...
Then there was the second set.
The infamous "booger" headshots.
좋아, 그것도 $500
500하고 500이면
Okay, so that's another $500.
That's 500 and 500. That's..
- 계산기 줘?
- 응
-You want a calculator?
-Please.
여깄다
Here.
또 뭐 있지?
All right, what else?
연기 수업, 무대 전투 수업
탭 댄스 수업
Well, there's acting classes,
stage-combat classes, tap classes..
그건 계속 비밀이다?
Which we're still keeping
under our hats.
사투리 선생한테
남부 말씨 배운 것도 있고
That dialect coach who helped you
with a Southern accent.
20시간이나 배웠어도
계속 자메이카 억양이었잖아
Which, after 20 hours of lessons,
still came out Jamaican.
뭔 소리야?
남부의 시대가 다시 온당께
What the hell are you talking about?
The South will rise again, man.
퍽이나 돈들인 보람이 있다
Yes, money well-spent.
좋아, 또 뭐? 방값
Okay, what else? Rent.
2년, 3년치 방값하고
전기세, 밥값
Two, three years of rent,
utilities, food..
좋아
내가 수표 써 줄 금액이
Okay, so I'm writing you
a check for..
내 영화 보다가 잤다구?
큰 잘못도 아니네
So you fell asleep during my movie.
Big deal, right?
빚 다 갚은 걸로 할까?
How do you clear this thing?
그거 다 먹어
Finish your enchilada.
로스, 매운 음식은 다 먹어봤잖아
소용없어
Ross, we've tried all the spicy food.
It's not working.
좋아, 그럼 이 고추 하나 먹어봐
Okay, here, have one of these peppers.
으악, 진짜 맵다, 오 하나님
Oh, God. So hot. Oh, my God.
고추 만지고 절대 눈 비비지 마
By the way, you don't want to touch
the pepper and then touch your eye.
아무것도 안 느껴져
I am feeling nothing.
너 그런 거 보니까
Speaking of hot,
watching you do that..
정말 너랑 자고 싶어진다
really makes me want
to have sex with you.
- 그만 해
- 제발! 시간 낭비하지 말자
-Stop it.
-Come on! Why are we wasting time?
효과가 있대잖아
의사가 권장한 거야
We know it's gonna work.
It's doctor-recommended.
미안하지만 선은 분명히
그어야 해... 아이구 매워
I'm sorry. But we have to have
some boundaries. My God, I'm dying.
예전에도 했던 거고
그냥 한 번 더 하는 것 뿐이야
We've done it before.
We'll do it again.
임신을 끝내는
아주 좋은 방법이라구
It'll be a nice way
to bookend the pregnancy.
단지 출산을 촉진하려고
사랑을 나누진 않을거야
I'm not gonna make love to you
so you'll go into labor.
사랑을 나눠? 니가 여자애냐?
Make love? What are you, a girl?
항상 그런 식으로 남자 옷을
벗기려고 하지
Always a great way to get
into a man's pants.
그냥 서비스하는 거야
나를 케첩병이라고 생각해
You'll be performing a service.
Think of me as a ketchup bottle.
케첩이 안나오면
병을 뒤에서 쳐야 되잖아
Sometimes, you have to bang on
the end of it to get it to come out.
참 사랑스러운 이야기다
I love when you talk dirty to me.
니 말이 옳아
별로 섹시한 말이 아니지
I know it. You're right.
That's not sexy.
오, 포크를 떨어뜨렸네
Oh, I seem to have dropped my fork.
허리 굽혀서 주워야지
Let me just bend over and get it.
아이구!
Oh, God!
됐어, 그만 해
아무리 그래도 안 할거야
Okay, enough.
This is not going to happen.
제발, 로스, 나 정말 비참해
Come on, Ross. I'm miserable here.
니가 시작한 거니까
니가 끝내야지!
Come on, you started this,
now you finish it!
빨리, 나한테 사랑을 나눠
Come on, wuss. Make love to me.
- 그거 알아?
- 뭘?
-You know what?
-What?
관 둬
Forget it.
뭐야, 이젠 나랑 말도
안 할거야?
What now, Ross,
you're not gonna talk?
도대체 왜 이렇게
화나게 하는거야?
How on earth will you ever annoy me?
오, 잠깐, 알겠다
Oh, wait a minute, I know.
넌 매운 고추 하나로 속을 다
비워낼 수 있다고 생각하나 본데
You'd think the jalapeno would
clear up your sinuses, but no!
그거로는 안돼...
지금 뭐 하는 거야?
That's not enough..
What are you doing?
아기 낳게 해줄게!
I'm getting that baby out of you!
- 오, 이런!
- 알아
-Oh, God!
-I know.
오, 잠깐, 잠깐
Oh, no, no, no.
양수가 터진 거 같애
I think my water just broke.
내 솜씨 끝내주네!
I am good!
베개 챙겼고, 가방도 있고
Okay, I got the pillow.
I got the bag.
- 열쇠는?
- 있어
-You got the keys?
-I got the keys.
정말 아기를 낳는구나
We're having a baby.
책에서 못 보긴 했는데
그거 할 시간이...?
I didn't have time to read this part
of the books, but do we have time..?
- 없어
- 알았어, 가자
-Not so much.
-Okay, let's go.
- 200
- 고마워
-200.
-Thank you.
이제 애가 언제 나오든 상관 안해
더 이상 내기는 안 할거야
That's it. I don't care when
the baby comes. No more betting.
좋아
Okay.
여보세요?
Hello?
내기 한 번만 더 하자
I guess we could bet
one more time.
- 레이첼이 애 낳는데?
- 어떻게 알았어?
-Is Rachel having the baby?
-How did you know that?
- 조이! 챈들러!
- 카페에 있어
-Joey! Chandler!
-They're at the coffee house.
모르는 게 없네!
You know everything!
아기 몸무게가
'3kg 넘는다'에 걸게
Wait. I bet you the baby
is over 7 pounds.
'머리카락이 있다'는 어때!
'딸이다'에 건다
I bet you it has hair!
I bet you it's a girl.
- 딸인 거 알잖아
- 너한테 정말 유리하게 해줄게
-We know it's a girl.
-I'll give you really good odds.